{
    "subject": "resource/Fazal_Malik_Akif",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Kohat",
    "human_readable": "Fazal Malik Akif was born in Kohat.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9011200070381165,
            "question": "Where was Fazal Malik Akif born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.840692400932312,
            "question": "Did Fazal Malik Akif live in Kohat his whole life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.805410623550415,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where Fazal Malik Akif was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7937533855438232,
            "question": "What is the significance of Kohat to Fazal Malik Akif?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7871837615966797,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the city where Fazal Malik Akif was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7679227590560913,
            "question": "Are there any notable events associated with Fazal Malik Akif's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6016616225242615,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Fazal Malik Akif's childhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5933478474617004,
            "question": "What is Fazal Malik Akif known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5609710216522217,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Fazal Malik Akif's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4130151569843292,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics of people born in Kohat?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fazal Malik Akif was born in Kohat.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7416_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Fazal Malik Akif's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7416_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Fazal Malik Akif known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7416_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Fazal Malik Akif's childhood?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7416_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7416_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7416_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7416_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7416_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7416_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7416_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7416_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7416_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7416_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7416_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this response is that Fazal Malik Akif's birthplace is mentioned as Kohat in the provided context information, which matches the statement in the query."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents mentions that \"Fazal Malik Akif\" was born on October 22, 1947, in Kohat. Therefore, the statement \"Fazal Malik Akif was born in Kohat\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}